[left hand] reach toward the domino | [right hand] reach toward the domino | [ego] stay still
[left hand] lift the domino upright | [right hand] lift the domino upright | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the domino on the table | [ego] stay still
[right hand] lift the domino upright | [ego] stay still
[left hand] lift the domino upright | [right hand] lift the domino upright | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the domino on the table | [right hand] place the domino on the table | [ego] stay still
[right hand] lift the domino upright | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the domino on the table | [ego] stay still
[right hand] lift the domino upright | [left hand] lift the domino upright | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the domino on the table | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the domino on the table | [ego] stay still
[left hand] topple the domino | [ego] stay still